<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Voices of Amerikua]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Voices of Amerikua]]></description>
        <link>http://www.voicesofamerikua.net/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 23:54:42 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://www.voicesofamerikua.net/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 23:54:41 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Join the Movement here]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Voices of Amerikua</strong> is a collaborative multimedia project and online platform dedicated to promoting efforts to protect the culture and rights of indigenous peoples and Mother Nature throughout North, Central and South America.</p>,<p><strong>Voices of Amerikua</strong> seeks to partner with filmmakers, media producers, activists, musicians and the indigenous communities themselves to create and share original media pieces that share the stories of these communities standing on the front lines of protecting our environment and their traditional cultures and ways of life.</p>,<p><strong>Voices of Amerikua</strong> was born out of the necessity to share and support the struggles of indigenous communities in North, Central and South America, which together speak more than 300 hundred languages.</p>,<p>Our mission is to edit, translate and produce original media in partnership specifically with Indigenous Nations, Leaders, Youth and Wisdom Keepers of North, Central and South America.We would like to help bring digital media tools to some of these communities to empower them to create their own original pieces so the original <strong>Voices of Amerikua</strong> can be heard by the entire world.</p>,<h3>Join the Movement <a href="http://www.voicesofamerikua.net/join-voices-of-amerikua-an-emerging-media-alliance-and-web-p" title="http://www.voicesofamerikua.net/join-voices-of-amerikua-an-emerging-media-alliance-and-web-p">here</a></h3>,<h3>Support Us <a href="http://www.voicesofamerikua.net/support-us" title="http://www.voicesofamerikua.net/support-us">here</a></h3>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.voicesofamerikua.net/about/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5a5faf5a-c15a-4767-af53-ade858e62a1a</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 03:49:31 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Indigenous Flood is Coming ! - April 24, 2017]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h2>Indigenous Flood is Coming ! - April 24, 2017</h2>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJxdkM1qwzAQhF_FCJKjfxLbBSdKKZS8gHsviryWRGStWclR8_ZV7ZwKexhmvxnYPZuRxASZJ8mZDmH2XVHEGPNRSLgh3nOJUzHbRRnni4cZAPNZz--aYOQrvzt-7A7XNP9Tyfo0ygRh-wnv0BvlhPXJXVv-RFVWTVs2bX2o66Z-q9vk7b3G-B3gJ_ByH80QNE8MyzbJVq3BKB04O1YNy3x4WuDshjQAdQ4dnPABNFqMnTbDAC4xktBa4xRnDlm2nrwFOEt9wib4i4TzsyBw8slZoAVei-tibS8JwL3sy7nYvnb5Bcq6bQo" height="308"></iframe>,<p>The 16th Annual United Nations Permanent Forum on Indigenous Issues starts today! Thanks to Mike Gamms and Joann Mae Spotted Bear for helping inspire many to stand together with the Indigenous Flood - United Nations : NYC event! Thank you to all our water protectors who contributed a video to this piece.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.voicesofamerikua.net/join-the-movement-here/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">04602178-c3e4-4bc7-8ce0-7140b20cecb4</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 21:35:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[22 of April #LandRightsNow]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h2>22 of April #LandRightsNow</h2>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/f103261e-4872-4dd2-9264-085d9ff0ccc6.jpg">,<p>EN ESPAÑOL</p>,<h2>This is a Global Call to Action for communities, organizations, governments, and individuals worldwide to promote and secure the land rights of Indigenous Peoples and local communities.</h2>,<h2>We are seeking champions that can lead by example in the global fight for land rights.</h2>,<p>Working together we can support the existing struggles of local communities and Indigenous Peoples in different parts of the world.</p>,<p>If you are an organization, you can:</p>,<p>➤ Sign-up on this platform and endorse our recommendations</p>,<p>➤ Scale-up your work on indigenous and community land rights and highlight your own activities via social media by using the hashtag #LandRightsNow</p>,<p>➤ Download the material from this website, including the logo, and use it to link to this international initiative</p>,<p>➤ Connect to other participants, create new collaborations, or simply join existing projects. Together we are stronger!</p>,<p>If you are a government, you can:</p>,<p>➤ Engage with participant civil society of your country, support the initiative, and identify concrete steps to advance indigenous and community land rights with them</p>,<p>If you are a citizen, you can:</p>,<p>➤ Sign-up, share this website with your friends, and stay informed on upcoming actions</p>,<p>➤ Follow us on Twitter or Facebook or post using hashtag #LandRightsNow</p>,<p>➤ Show your support by sending us a picture of your hands with the Land Rights Now logo using the hashtag #LandRightsNow</p>,<p>➤ Read more about land rights in your country</p>,<p>Join us in this journey and stay in touch!</p>,<p>For any question, you can contact: <a href="mailto:landrightsnow@gmail.com">landrightsnow@gmail.com</a></p>,<p>http://www.landrightsnow.org/en/get-involved/</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.voicesofamerikua.net/22-of-april-landrightsnow/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">10006a8f-efc1-4545-ada2-1e4d6701a864</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2017 01:40:20 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Land Rights Now]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Land Rights Now</h1><p>&#x27A4; Engage with participant civil society of your country, support the initiative, and identify concrete steps to advance indigenous and community land rights with them</p><img src="https://landrightsnow.contentfiles.net/media/assets/image/header-paddy-field.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.landrightsnow.org/en/get-involved/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3d45d35c-5128-4a24-9e5c-d9e9b5cfe5ea</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2017 18:20:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AWAKE - A Dream From Standing Rock [TRAILER]]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<iframe src="https://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?src=https%3A%2F%2Fplayer.vimeo.com%2Fvideo%2F209864938&url=https%3A%2F%2Fvimeo.com%2F209864938&image=https%3A%2F%2Fi.vimeocdn.com%2Fvideo%2F625639772_1280.jpg&key=b7d04c9b404c499eba89ee7072e1c4f7&type=text%2Fhtml&schema=vimeo" width="1000" height="563" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>,<article><h1>Awake, A Dream from Standing Rock</h1><p>From Directors Josh Fox, James Spione, Myron Dewey &amp; Executive Producer Shailene Woodley. Premiers April 22, 2017 at the Tribeca Film Festival and Available Everywhere Online for a donation.</p></article>,<blockquote>In 2016, Standing Rock, North Dakota became one of the most watched places on earth. Josh Fox James Spione Myron Dewey Digital Smoke Signals are honored to present a new documentary &apos;AWAKE, A Dream From Standing Rock,&apos; which captures some of the many stories of the Native-led resistance against the Dakota Access Pipeline, which forever changed the way people approach the fight for Indigenous sovereignty and the resistance to fossil fuel infrastructure, Big Oil and climate change.</blockquote>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.voicesofamerikua.net/awake-a-dream-from-standing-rock-trailer/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1642915c-c11c-48bd-b839-f7e0067e0a1a</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2017 03:18:09 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ecuadorian community fight off oil threats - If Not Us Then Who?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Voices of Amerikua featured in “If Not Us Then Who”</p>,<article><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/0bfac9c904ed32b00cfa1953f726e04636ca53cc.jpg"><h1>Ecuadorian community fight off oil threats - If Not Us Then Who?</h1><p>The community of Morete Cocha is located in the region of Pastaza Province in the Amazon region of Ecuador. Like many other communities Morete Cocha is under threat by interest of oil companies seeking to exploit crude in the communities land. This is the story of community&apos;s search for environmental and cultural preservation.http://ifnotusthenwho.me/films/ecuadorian-community-fight-off-oil-threats/</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.voicesofamerikua.net/ecuadorian-community-fight-off-oil-threats-if-not-us-then/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0bf3d36a-955d-4456-96ea-b6ab954bb9fe</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 23:39:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Voices of Amerikua in Native Spirit Film Festival]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Voices of Amerikua in Native Spirit Film Festival</h1>,<p>We are pleased to announce that our short film on Moretecocha commmunity in Ecuador will be shown tomorrow at the Bookclub EC2 as part of the Native Spirit Film Festival in London, England.</p>,<article><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/91d9e6fd1bfaf4286ce0a1fab0455e175230e606.jpg"><h1>Festival highlights: Films from Amazon to Artic and special selection of Shorts from Wapikoni Mobile and Winnipeg Film Group</h1><p>Join us for a Sunday sojourn celebrating Film and Culture Indigenous style, including special showcase of Wapikoni Mobile and Winnipeg Film Group Shorts, all by Native filmmakers, with open invitation to Indigenous guests, musicians, artists and speakers attending the rest of our festival 7-16 October and available nearer the time.This is a rare opportunity to see Indigenous cinema and hear stories direct - open to everyone, invite your friends!</p></article>,<article><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/3b91768345ac91ef727dd9cfa17cb093abdcc41b.jpg"><h1>Welcome to Native Spirit Foundation - Native Spirit Foundation</h1><p>Native Spirit Foundation is the UK&apos;s only Independent, non-profit organisation promoting knowledge and awareness of Indigenous Cultures. We hold an annual Film Festival in London with talks and performances celebrating Indigenous culture, and work towards supporting education in Indigenous Schools and Communities.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thebookclub.eventcube.io/events/4850/festival-highlights-films-from-amazon-to-artic-and-special-selection-of-shorts-from-wapikoni-mobile-and-winnipeg-film-group</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b0914494-04a9-471b-b3d8-e5301f32eecb</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2016 00:26:16 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Media]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Media</h1>,<p>Voices of Amerikua - Berito Kuwaruwa (Cobaría), Pueblo U'Wa - Colombia</p>,<iframe src="https://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?src=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fembed%2FORa5hgKfQsQ%3Ffeature%3Doembed&url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DORa5hgKfQsQ&image=https%3A%2F%2Fi.ytimg.com%2Fvi%2FORa5hgKfQsQ%2Fhqdefault.jpg&key=b7d04c9b404c499eba89ee7072e1c4f7&type=text%2Fhtml&schema=youtube" width="640" height="360" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>,<p><em>First Episode of “Voices of Amerikua” featuring different indigenous voices from the americas in defense of their culture, territory and mother nature.</em></p>,<p>Berito Kuwaruwa is a leader of the U’wa indigenous community in Colombia</p>,<p>Berito Kuwaruwa launched an international non-violent campaign calling on the multinational oil to protest drilling in the ancestral lands of the U’wa people, who believe oil is the blood of Mother Earth. He received the Goldman Environmental Prize in 1998. See:<a href="http://www.goldmanprize.org/recipient/berito-kuwaruwa/">http://www.goldmanprize.org/recipient/berito-kuwaruwa/</a></p>,<p>As a child Berito was kidnapped by Catholic missionaries and taken to live on a mission . He lived in the mission for several years until his mother rescued him. As a result of that experience Berito has been working in defense of their people from an early age .</p>,<p>More information:</p>,<p><a href="http://amazonwatch.org/news/2015/0624-bad-faith-colombian-government-disrespects-uwa-people">http://amazonwatch.org/news/2015/0624-bad-faith-colombian-government-disrespects-uwa-people</a></p>,<p>Voices of Amerikua | Moretecocha - Ecuador</p>,<iframe src="https://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?src=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fembed%2FbPjxUqO2dfg%3Ffeature%3Doembed&url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DbPjxUqO2dfg&image=https%3A%2F%2Fi.ytimg.com%2Fvi%2FbPjxUqO2dfg%2Fhqdefault.jpg&key=b7d04c9b404c499eba89ee7072e1c4f7&type=text%2Fhtml&schema=youtube" width="640" height="360" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>,<p>Visit this page for more for more information on how to support the community!</p>,<p><a href="https://www.gofundme.com/a73ycqmc?utm_source=internal&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_content=body_photo&amp;utm_campaign=upd_n" title="https://www.gofundme.com/a73ycqmc?utm_source=internal&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_content=body_photo&amp;utm_campaign=upd_n">https://www.gofundme.com/a73ycqmc?utm_source=internal&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_content=body_photo&amp;utm_campaign=upd_n</a></p>,<p>ENGLISH: The community of Morete Cocha is located in the region of Pastaza Province in the Amazon region of Ecuador. Like many other communities Morete Cocha is under threat by interest of oil companies seeking to exploit crude in the communities land.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.voicesofamerikua.net/media/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2df895e4-9bab-42b7-b439-41e38d77df42</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2017 02:59:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Roots Awaken | Official Trailer (HD) | Las Raíces Despiertan]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>The Roots Awaken</p>,<iframe src="https://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?src=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fembed%2FYnM6ftqAQD8%3Ffeature%3Doembed&url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DYnM6ftqAQD8&image=https%3A%2F%2Fi.ytimg.com%2Fvi%2FYnM6ftqAQD8%2Fhqdefault.jpg&key=b7d04c9b404c499eba89ee7072e1c4f7&type=text%2Fhtml&schema=youtube" width="640" height="360" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YnM6ftqAQD8</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">fdb9ebc1-66d5-4f89-abc1-efd4f1fd8406</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2017 03:31:48 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Support us]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/2b2431f8e7ba7b0/72cf7928ed1d9f9c298879239b126d29/croprotate.jpg?cropheight=2591&cropwidth=3872&degrees=0&input=https%3A%2F%2Fthe-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com%2F15db3d51-f7be-4498-8840-81f2fa5dea93.jpg&x=0&y=0">,<h1>Support us</h1>,<h1><strong>We Need Your Support !/ Necesitamos Tu Apoyo !</strong></h1>,<h2><strong>ENGLISH:</strong></h2>,<p><strong>Webmasters and developers out there: We are seeking support in making a wordpress video blog site for a soon-to-be-released website for Voices of Amerikua, a media alliance and transmedia project dedicated to sharing the voice of indigenous people working to protect their culture, territories, and Mother Nature in North, Central and South America. Website will be in English, Spanish and Portuguese.</strong></p>,<p><strong>We have found a cool wordpress video blog template that would be ideal for this <a href="https://themeforest.net/item/videotouch-video-wordpress-theme/9340715?ref=athemez" title="">https://themeforest.net/item/videotouch-video-wordpress-theme/9340715?ref=athemez</a><br>Do any of you have a template they can offer as a donation?</strong></p>,<p><strong>Any support or advice is appreciated.</strong></p>,<p><strong>Voices of Amerikua Team</strong></p>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.voicesofamerikua.net/support-us/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">aa1d866f-f80b-4b08-8036-2efbab3a96ba</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2016 00:18:35 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>